<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Highway to the Gopher Zone</title>
    <link>http://gopher.zone/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Highway to the Gopher Zone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 21:09:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gopher.zone/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Gopher</title>
      <link>http://gopher.zone/posts/how-to-gopher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 21:09:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gopher.zone/posts/how-to-gopher/</guid>
      <description>Originally published by dbucklin at gopher://sdf.org:70/0/users/dbucklin/posts/how_gopher.txt
 From: dbucklin@sdf.org Date: 2018-03-31 Subject: How to Gopher In principal, publishing a Gopher site should be easy. And it *is* easy, assuming you are willing to put in some effort. At minimum, you need to find someone who is already operating a Gopher server, find out how to get access to the server, and then create, orga- nize, and upload your content. At most, you need to set up a gopher server -- not just the daemon, but set up a server or VPS with the appropriate operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Can I Setup My Gopherspace</title>
      <link>http://gopher.zone/posts/how-can-i-setup-my-gopherspace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 21:01:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gopher.zone/posts/how-can-i-setup-my-gopherspace/</guid>
      <description>Original published by SDF at gopher://sdf.org:70/1/sdf/faq/GOPHER
The article in this content is specific to setting up a gopher hole on SDF (The Super Dimensional Fortress) Public Access Unix System. Visit sdf.org for more information on how to create an account.
HOW CAN I SETUP MY GOPHERSPACE? This document was written with &amp;lsquo;mkgopher&amp;rsquo; in mind. You may be managing your space from the UNIX shell, but since &amp;lsquo;mkgopher&amp;rsquo; uses common UNIX commands, this should still be helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Gopher and Gopherspace</title>
      <link>http://gopher.zone/posts/what-is-gopher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 20:49:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gopher.zone/posts/what-is-gopher/</guid>
      <description>Original published by SDF at gopher://sdf.org:70/1/sdf/faq/GOPHER
WHAT IS GOPHER AND GOPHERSPACE? GOPHER is a network protocol that enables multiple servers to create a single, uniform filesystem that transcends system architecure and operating systems (GOPHERSPACE). With GOPHER, information holds the most value. Since presentation is uniform across GOPHERSPACE, the user does not encounter any challenges in &amp;lsquo;learning&amp;rsquo; a new site. Because of its simplicity and its emphasis on the importance of informational texts, GOPHER is ideal for those who are visually impared.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>